Thanks, everyone.
I -- I...I spend... what I would call an inordinate amount of time on the Internet, doing really stupid things.
Doing things that I'm n-- like replying to e-mails that are not necessarily meant for me.
I -- I have, uh -- I have veitch@domain.com for my e-mail address.
And what that means is that, if someone misses off the initial, I get the e-mail.
So, I get a lot of e-mails for Veitchs who, I have no idea who they are.
I got an e-mail that was addressed to Alan and Deb Veitch.
I have literally no idea who these people are.
But it said "Please review the cash estimate."
And it was from a -- It was a company -- It was a swimming-pool company.
A guy called, basically, Lex... runs a company called Relex Pools.
And the pool was 102 LF, right?
And I thought -- I thought I'd test the water, so to speak...
...and I said, "Look, what does LF, uh -- What does LF stand for?"
And... they got back in touch.
And they said, "LF stands for 'linear feet.'"
Janice... did not seem to mind or notice the fact that I was neither Alan nor Deb.
I thought, "That's interesting."
She said, "See attached plans."
Now, she attached these plans of the proposed swimming pool.
So, basically, you guys, you've got, here -- You've got the, uh...
We've got the neighboring houses, some foliage, and up at the top left we've got this -- Alan and Deb's house.
And then, that's the proposed pool.
And I want to be very clear about this, guys -- you should never reply to an e-mail that's not meant for you.
You shouldn't do it.
Why?
Because you should just delete the e-mail, let the people know they've made a terrible mistake.
However... looking at that... I don't know about you, but to me... I just didn't think Alan and Deb were gonna be happy with that.
I said "Janice, I'm gonna be frank..."
"...I'm unhappy with the size of the pool." "
"Mr. Veitch, it's not legal to build on private property."
"The pool is as large as it can be without encroaching on your neighbor's property." "
I said, "Old Man McPhearson?"
"He won't mind." "
I said, "We're still skimping on the size of the pool.
I don't want people to come around and be like, 'Where's the pool?'" "
"Balls on the line, Janice."
"It needs to be larger." "
She said, "How much larger?"
I said, "Boom."
"That is not possible." "
No [bleep], Janice.
"We cannot build that close to the property." "
"Well, if the property is a problem, I'll take out the property." "
I'll be honest -- I thought, based upon that, that she would know that I was joking.
"Where will you live?" "
I said, "Boom."
James Veitch. Look out for his comedy special later this year. James Veitch。